HELLO.
WHAT'S THIS?
OH, RIGHT, IT'S THAT GIRL'S
PHONE NUMBER.
( sighs )
YEAH, YEAH, THERE IT IS.
JUST A PHONE NUMBER
A REALLY HOT GIRL GAVE ME.
( chuckling )
IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
I MEAN, IT IS HER HOME
PHONE NUMBER, BUT...
WHOA!
WH-WHOOPS.
( chuckling )
ALMOST LOST THIS BABY.
YEAH, THE LOVELY AMANDA
GIVES ME HER NUMBER
AND I, I GO AND DROP IT.
( chuckles )
( sneezes )
THANK YOU.
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN YOUR DAY ♪
♪ YOUR WEEK, YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ WHEN THE RAIN
STARTS TO POUR ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ LIKE I'VE BEEN THERE BEFORE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
RACHEL?
YEAH.
WHEN'S YOUR BIRTHDAY?
MAY 5. WHY?
I'M JUST MAKING A LIST
OF PEOPLE'S BIRTHDAYS.
OH, MINE'S DECEMBER...
YEAH, WHATEVER.
Chandler:
OH, SHE'S PRETTY.
PRETTY, UH, PRETTY GIRL.
THE PRETTY...
SHE'S PRETTY.
WELL, JUST GO UP TO
HER AND ASK HER OUT.
WHAT'S THE WORST THING
THAT COULD HAPPEN?
I COULD DIE.
YEAH, IT'S...
IT'S TOUGH BEING SINGLE.
THAT'S WHY I'M SO GLAD
I FOUND AMANDA.
ROSS, YOU GUYS WENT OUT ONCE.
YOU TOOK YOUR KIDS
TO CHUCK E CHEESE
AND YOU DIDN'T EVEN KISS HER.
I TELL PEOPLE SECRETS.
IT MAKES THEM LIKE ME.
OH.
HEY.
( sneezes )
OH, PHOEBE, YOU'RE SICK.
YOU SHOULDN'T PLAY.
YOU SHOULD JUST GO HOME
AND GET IN BED AND STAY THERE.
BUT I'M UNEMPLOYED.
MY MUSIC IS ALL I
REALLY HAVE NOW.
WELL, MUSIC AND
MAKING MY OWN SHOES.
PRETTY, HUH?
( sneezes )
ALL RIGHT.
I'M GOING TO DO IT.
I'M GOING TO GO
GET SHOT DOWN.
A-ANY ADVICE?
JUST BE YOURSELF.
BUT NOT TOO MUCH.
WISH ME LUCK.
( loudly ):
GOOD LUCK.
WISH IT.
HI. HI, I-I WAS JUST, UH,
SITTING OVER THERE AND...
UH, CHANDLER.
MY NAME'S CHANDLER.
DID I SAY THAT?
NO, YOU DIDN'T.
HI, I'M KATHY.
KATHY WITH
A "K" OR A "C"?
WITH A "K."
H-H-HEY!
WOW. YOU ARE
REALLY GOOD AT THIS.
HEY, COME ON,
GIVE ME A BREAK.
I'M OUT ON A LIMB HERE.
I'M SORRY. YOU'RE RIGHT.
I APOLOGIZE,
BUT I SHOULD TELL YOU
THAT I'M WAITING
FOR A DATE.
OH, AND THERE HE IS NOW.
HEY!
HEY! HEY-HEY, HEY.
I SEE YOU GUYS
ALREADY MET, HUH?
YES, YES. I WAS JUST
TRYING TO FIGURE OUT A WAY
TO DEMONSTRATE HOW I CAN GET
MY EXCEPTIONALLY LARGE FEET
INTO MY EVEN BIGGER MOUTH.
DIDN'T I TELL YOU?
ALWAYS SHOWING OFF.
( chuckles )
I... BEFORE I START I JUST
WANT TO SAY THAT I HAVE A COLD.
SO IF I SNEEZE
IN THE MIDDLE OF A SONG
IT'S NOT ON PURPOSE.
OH, EXCEPT THE LAST VERSE
OF "PEPPER PEOPLE."
OKAY?
( clears throat )
( rasping ):
♪ SMELLY CAT ♪
♪ WHAT ARE
THEY FEEDING YOU...? ♪
THIS CHICK SOUNDS GOOD.
♪ SMELLY CAT,
SMELLY... ♪
HEY, GUNTHER,
BE A GOOD LITTLE BOY
AND BRING ME
A WHISKEY.
HI.
GEEZ, AT 2:30
IN THE MORNING
I DIDN'T EXPECT TO HAVE
TO FIGHT OVER THE REMOTE.
SORRY. THERE'S THIS
ERNIE KOVACS THING
ON IN A FEW MINUTES
I WANTED TO WATCH.
MY GOD, THAT'S WHY
I GOT UP, TOO.
YOU'RE KIDDING?
OH, I LOVE HIM.
HEY, LISTEN, I'M SORRY
ABOUT THIS AFTERNOON.
YOU KNOW, IF I HAD
KNOWN YOU GUYS WERE...
I NEVER WOULD'VE...
( chuckling ):
OH, PLEASE!
SO, JOEY TELLS ME
YOU TWO MET IN ACTING CLASS.
YEAH, THEY TEAMED US UP
AS PARTNERS
AND JOEY PICKED THREE SCENES
FOR US TO DO.
ALL OF THEM HAD US MAKING OUT.
THAT'S A GOOD THING,
ACTUALLY
BECAUSE, UH, HE USED
TO MAKE ME REHEARSE WITH HIM.
OH-OH-OH-OH-OH!
OH, IS IT ON?
NO, BUT THIS WONDER
BROOM IS AMAZING!
HEY, WAIT.
( gasps )
OH, MY GOD!
OH, IT'S ON, IT'S ON.
( music-box song playing )
HERE WE GO,
LITTLE FELLA.
( giggles )
WHAT ABOUT THE DUCK?
WELL, THE DUCK CAN SWIM.
OF COURSE.
( throaty voice ):
♪ MY STICKY SHOE ♪
♪ MY STICKY, STICKY SHOE ♪
♪ WHY YOU STICK ON ME ♪
♪ BABY? ♪
THANKS FOR THE LIGHTS, HONEY.
Ross:
WAY TO GO.
YOUR COLD MAKES YOU
SOUND SO GREAT.
IT'S FUN.
GOD, I LOVE HOW SEXY I AM.
( coughing )
KATH, WE SHOULD
GET GOING.
WE'RE GOING TO BUY HAMSTERS.
OH...
I LOVE THOSE LITTLE GUYS.
NO, NO, IT'S
NOT LIKE THAT.
I... I WORK FOR A
MEDICAL RESEARCHER.
WELL, HAVE FUN.
OKAY.
WELL, I THINK IT'S NICE
THAT THE MEDICAL COMMUNITY
IS FINALLY TRYING
TO HELP SICK HAMSTERS.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I LIKE KATHY.
YEAH?
OH, YEAH, ME, TOO.
SHE'S SO COOL AND PRETTY.
Phoebe:
YEAH, SHE'S...
SHE'S SMART AND...
FUNNY, YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, WE WERE UP
ALL LAST NIGHT TALKING.
SHE SAID
THE FUNNIEST THING
ABOUT-- WHAT?
YOU LOVE HER.
NO, I DON'T.
YES, YOU DO.
CHANDLER LOVES KATHY.
COME ON, PHEEBS,
NOW, JUST-- JUST LAY OFF HIM.
THANK YOU, ROSS.
YEAH, HE'S A LITTLE
SENSITIVE RIGHT NOW
BECAUSE HE'S SO IN LOVE.
ALL RIGHT.
( all making kissing noises )
OH, MM!
OH, KATHY!
KATHY,
I LOVE YOU.
OH!
( making kissing noises )
Phoebe:
SO, I NEED TO WRITE
SOME DEPRESSING STUFF TO GO
WITH MY NEW BLUESY VOICE
BUT NOTHING THAT SAD
HAS EVER REALLY HAPPENED TO ME.
WELL, HOW ABOUT YOUR MOM DYING
OR HAVING TO LIVE ON THE STREETS
WHEN YOU WERE 14?
UH-HUH.
OH, YEAH,
I COULD WRITE ABOUT THE TIME
MY HAIR DID
THAT WHOO-HOO THING.
HEY.
( both ):
SO, I'M GOING
OVER TO AMANDA'S TONIGHT...
RACHEL'S NOT HERE.
OH.
HOW'S IT GOING WITH HER?
GREAT, ACTUALLY.
I'M THINKING TONIGHT
MAY BE THE NIGHT.
YEAH, THE KIDS ARE GOING
TO PLAY TOGETHER
AND THEN,
WHEN THEY'RE ASLEEP
I'M THINKING AMANDA AND I
BREAK OPEN A BOTTLE OF WINE--
DO A LITTLE PLAYING
OURSELVES.
HI, GUYS.
THIS IS JOSH.
JOSH, THESE
ARE MY FRIENDS.
AND THAT'S ROSS.
HI, JOSH.
HI.
DUDES.
DID YOU PLAY IN COLLEGE?
OH, I STILL DO.
NEXT YEAR I HOPE
TO MAKE VARSITY, THOUGH.
ROSS, DIDN'T YOU
PLAY SOCCER
IN HIGH SCHOOL?
OH, NO, WAIT,
THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU JUST ORGANIZED
THEIR GAME SCHEDULES
ON YOUR COMMODORE 64.
WELL, IT'S GETTING LATE.
I GOT TO GET TO THE GAME,
SO I'M GOING TO HEAD.
OKAY.
I'LL MISS YOU.
DOPE!
WOW. CUTE ONE.
VERY CUTE.
I KNOW. ISN'T HE GREAT?
IT'S SO NICE
TO FINALLY BE
IN A FUN RELATIONSHIP,
YOU KNOW?
NOTHING BORING ABOUT HIM,
AND, UH...
BET HE'S NEVER EVEN
SET FOOT IN A MUSEUM.
WELL, MAYBE HE'LL GET
TO GO SOON--
YOU KNOW, LIKE
ON A CLASS TRIP OR SOMETHING.
YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE IS
REALLY GREAT ABOUT HIM?
OH, WHAT IS THE
WORD FOR AN ADULT
WHO DOESN'T HAVE
DINOSAUR TOYS IN
THEIR BEDROOM?
OH...
WHAT WAS THAT?
MONICA KNOWS.
IT'S THIS DUMB THING
THAT ROSS MADE UP
TO TRY TO FOOL OUR PARENTS.
IT'S A WAY OF GIVING THE FINGER
WITHOUT ACTUALLY HAVING
TO GIVE IT.
I REMEMBER I CRIED
THE NIGHT YOU MADE THAT UP.
IT WAS THE FIRST TIME
I REALIZED I WAS COOLER
THAN MY BIG BROTHER.
WELL.
I'M GOING TO GO GET READY...
FOR MY DATE TONIGHT, SO, UH...
I'LL JUST HEAD.
YEAH, I SHOULD GO, TOO,
'CAUSE I'M PLAYING IN ONE HOUR.
( clears throat )
( normal voice ):
YOU GUYS SHOULD COME HEAR ME.
OOH! HEAR ME-- OOH!
♪ MY STICKY SHOES... ♪
EWW! EWW! OH!
I LOST MY SEXY PHLEGM.
HI.
HI, BEN.
WOW, YOU-- YOU LOOK GREAT.
THANKS.
OKAY. HEY, TOMMY.
I AM SO GLAD
THAT YOU COULD
COME OVER TONIGHT.
OH, NO, NO.
IT'S MY PLEASURE.
MY CELL PHONE NUMBER
IS RIGHT HERE ON THE COUNTER.
PLEASE HELP YOURSELF TO
ANYTHING IN THE FRIDGE.
WHA--
I APPRECIATE THIS SO MUCH.
I HAVE BEEN TRYING TO
GO OUT WITH THIS GUY
FOR, LIKE, A MONTH.
I-I DON'T...
OH, I DON'T MEAN
TO BE A SQUARE
BUT I'D REALLY APPRECIATE IT
IF YOU'D WAIT
AND DRINK YOUR WINE
AFTER THE KIDS ARE ASLEEP.
GOODNIGHT, SWEETIE.
OH, THANKS FOR THIS.
I HOPE I CAN DO THE
SAME FOR YOU SOMETIME.
( sighs )
WHO WANTS TO MAKE
SOME LONG-DISTANCE CALLS?
KATHY!
KATHY! HI!
KATHY! KATHY!
KATHY!
FETCH! FETCH IT!
( breathlessly ):
KA... KATHY.
HEY. CHANDLER,
WHAT'RE YOU DOING HERE?
WELL...
I JUST WANTED TO SAY, "HEY."
HEY.
OKAY.
( whimpers )
YOU'RE MAKING IT SOUND
WORSE THAN IT WAS.
HER DATE TIPPED ME TEN DOLLARS.
PHEEBS, WHAT
ARE YOU DOING?
OKAY, I WANT
TO BE SEXY AGAIN
SO, I'M TRYING
TO CATCH A COLD.
SHOULD BE EASY. SUPPOSEDLY,
THEY'RE PRETTY COMMON.
PHOEBE,
YOU'LL CATCH PNEUMONIA.
OKAY, YOU WERE RIGHT.
I'M IN LOVE
WITH JOEY'S GIRLFRIEND.
WHAT?
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
HOW IS THAT POSSIBLE?
YOU BARELY KNOW HER.
I DON'T KNOW.
I CAN'T... I JU...
I CAN'T GET HER OUT OF MY HEAD,
YOU KNOW?
I MEAN, I'M A VERY BAD PERSON.
I'M A VERY, VERY BAD PER...
I'M A HORRIBLE PERSON.
NO, YOU'RE NOT, CHANDLER.
WE STILL LOVE YOU, CHANDLER.
( sneezes )
OH... GOSH, PHOEBE,
I THINK
I CAUGHT
YOUR COLD.
YOU MEAN YOU STOLE IT.
( sneezes )
DON'T COVER YOUR MOUTH
WHEN YOU DO THAT.
( both laughing )
OH...
WE WERE JUST TALKING
ABOUT YOU.
REALLY.
YEAH, I TOLD HER ABOUT
THE TIME YOU GOT DRUNK
AND FELL ASLEEP WITH
YOUR HEAD IN THE TOILET.
( laughing )
RIGHT IN THERE.
...NINETY-NINE
A HUNDRED.
READY OR NOT, HERE I COME!
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO OVER
THE CONCEPT ONE MORE TIME.
HEY.
LISTEN, YOU WANT
TO GET SOME DINNER
WITH ME AND KATHY
TONIGHT?
OH, UM, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I, UH, ALREADY ATE.
IT'S 4:30.
YEAH, WELL, I HAD A
BIG MEAL ON MONDAY.
SO THAT'S JUST
GOING TO GET ME
STRAIGHT THROUGH
THE WEEK.
OKAY.
I SEE WHAT'S GOING ON HERE.
YOU, YOU DO?
YEAH. YOU DON'T LIKE KATHY.
YOU GOT ME.
YEAH. YOU BEEN
AVOIDING HER
EVER SINCE
WE STARTED GOING OUT.
I MADE AN EFFORT
TO LIKE JANICE.
IT'S YOUR TURN
TO MAKE AN EFFORT TO LIKE KATHY
BY COMING OUT TO DINNER WITH US.
RIGHT?
YEAH, RIGHT.
GOOD. AND, HEY, MY TREAT.
BUT THAT'S ONLY BECAUSE YOU'RE
NOT EATING ANYTHING, RIGHT?
RIGHT.
ROSS ISN'T HERE.
OH.
STOP IT!
SO, UH, I'LL SEE YOU
AT THE PARTY?
FEAR'S FEAR, MAN!
TWENTY-FOUR/SEVEN!
YEAH!
I AM SO GOING TO MARRY THAT GUY.
OH!
WHAT?
I THINK HE'S STEALING FROM ME.
WHY?
BECAUSE HE'S STEALING FROM ME.
OH!
HI. IT'S ME.
AND SOUP.
HEY, OH, I JUST SAW JOSH.
HE LOOKED SO YUMMY
IN YOUR LEATHER JACKET.
UGH!
HERE. NOW,
I DON'T EAT CHICKEN
SO, IT'S JUST NOODLE SOUP.
AND THERE'S
NO CHICKEN
IN THE BROTH EITHER
SO, IT'S REALLY
JUST NOODLE WATER.
THANK YOU SO MUCH,
PHOEBE.
SURE.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING WITH THOSE?
I NEED YOUR GERMS.
I WANT MY COLD BACK.
I MISS MY SEXY VOICE.
SORRY, PHOEBE.
THAT'S OKAY.
HOW'S THE SOUP?
MMM.
OHH!
GOD!
GROSS!
( laughing )
OH, MY GOD, YOU GUYS,
CHECK IT OUT.
YOU CAN SEE
THAT GIRL'S UNDERWEAR.
IS SHE GREAT OR WHAT?
SO? HUH?
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
UH, SHE'S, SHE'S
NOT REALLY MY TYPE.
NOT YOUR TYPE?
SHE'S GORGEOUS.
YOU KNOW WHAT
I THINK IT IS?
I THINK IT'S THE FISHNET
STOCKINGS, YOU KNOW?
WHENEVER I SEE A GIRL
IN FISHNET STOCKINGS
IT REMINDS ME OF...
MY FATHER IN
FISHNET STOCKINGS.
OKAY.
UNDERSTANDING
A LITTLE MORE OF
WHY YOU'RE SINGLE.
YOU KNOW, I HAVE
A FRIEND YOU'D LIKE.
SHE'S REALLY PRETTY,
AND THEN WE COULD
DOUBLE DATE.
UH, NO, NO, THANKS.
OKAY. I'VE GOT
SOME UGLY FRIENDS
AND THEY'RE
ALL AVAILABLE, TOO.
LISTEN, I'M GOING
TO GRAB A BEER.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK, OKAY?
WHAT WAS THAT?
WHAT?
KATHY WAS BEING NICE,
AND YOU WALKED AWAY.
I THOUGHT WE HAD A DEAL.
LOOK, WHAT DO
YOU WANT FROM ME?
I WANT YOU TO LIKE HER
BUT IF THAT'S TOO DAMN
DIFFICULT FOR YOU
THEN THE LEAST
YOU COULD DO IS PRETEND.
I AM PRETENDING.
WELL, THEN DO IT BETTER.
WHAT DO YOU SAY
I GO AND TELL HER
HOW MUCH I LIKE HER?
NO, NO. IT'LL BE GOOD.
I CAN TELL HER I BEEN
THINKING ABOUT HER--
THAT I HAVEN'T STOPPED
THINKING ABOUT HER
SINCE THE MOMENT WE MET
THAT I'M SO
FANTASTICALLY
OVER-THE-TOP
WANT-TO-SLIT-MY-OWN-
THROAT IN LOVE WITH HER
THAT FOR EVERY MINUTE OF
EVERY HOUR OF EVERY DAY
I CAN'T BELIEVE
MY OWN BAD LUCK THAT
YOU MET HER FIRST!
YEAH, WELL,
THAT'S PRETTY GOOD.
BUT YOU MIGHT WANT
TO TONE IT DOWN A LITTLE.
HEY.
SO, UH, AMANDA JUST,
JUST DROPPED ME OFF.
YOU KNOW, THAT'S ONE
OF THE THINGS
I LOVE ABOUT HER.
SHE'S, UH,
SHE'S OLD ENOUGH TO DRIVE.
SO, UH, I GUESS
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO MOM
AND DAD'S TONIGHT, HUH?
( coughing ):
NO, SORRY.
WELL, WHERE'S AMANDA?
COULD YOU GET ME
SOME COUGH DROPS?
YOU KNOW, I'M THINKING
YOU COULD BRING HER
AND YOU GUYS COULD GO
UP TO YOUR OLD ROOM
AND NOT MAKE OUT.
( coughing )
ROSS, A COUGH
DROP, PLEASE?
AT LEAST I KNOW
SHE'S NOT GOING OUT WITH ME
TO GET INTO "R"-RATED MOVIES.
( coughing )
WHY DON'T YOU
JUST MARRY HER?
OH, NO, WAIT A MINUTE.
YOU CAN'T. I'M SORRY.
I FORGOT.
SHE'S NOT A LESBIAN.
SEE, AMANDA
AND I HAVE A...
YOU HAVE NOTHING!
YOU'RE NOT EVEN GOING OUT.
YOU'RE HER BABY-SITTER.
YOU HAVE
A 12-YEAR-OLD GIRL'S JOB.
( laughing )
OH, THAT IS SO SAD.
AND WHAT ARE YOU LAUGHING AT
MISS "MY KEG-SUCKING BOYFRIEND
IS STEALING FROM ME"?
( stifled laugh )
SO HE STOLE A COUPLE BUCKS
FROM ME.
BIG DEAL.
HE BOUGHT ME SOMETHING
WITH IT.
THAT'S MINE!
NOW, WOULD YOU BOTH
PLEASE START ACTING LIKE ADULTS?
AND GET ME MY COUGH DROPS?
FINE.
SORRY.
HERE.
THANK YOU.
( sighs )
LEAST I MADE TEN BUCKS
IN MY RELATIONSHIP.
YOU KNOW...
♪ PARADING GOATS ARE PARADING ♪
♪ PARADING DOWN THE STREET ♪
♪ LEAVING LITTLE TREATS. ♪
I DON'T KNOW.
DOES IT EVEN WORK
WITHOUT MY SEXY VOICE?
I LIKE IT.
( sneezes )
GUNTHER, KISS ME.
W-WHAT?
( Kathy giggling )
( turns up volume )
HEY.
NOW, WE'RE NOT EXACTLY
GOING TO BE SLEEPING IN HERE
BUT DO YOU MIND?
( door shuts )
CAN I SLEEP ON YOUR COUCH?
♪ AND I'M STILL WAITING
FOR MY PAPIER-MáCHé MAN. ♪
THANK YOU, MY BABIES.
RACHEL?
YEAH.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU HEARD
ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED
BETWEEN ME AND PHOEBE
THE OTHER DAY.
NO.
WELL, WE KISSED.
I-I DIDN'T INITIATE
THE KISS
BUT, BUT I ALSO
DIDN'T STOP IT, AND...
I'VE BEEN FEELING GUILTY.
OKAY.
SO, UM...
ARE WE COOL?
OKAY.
I KNEW YOU'D UNDERSTAND.